Guide to the McKim Mead and White Architectural Records circa 1875-1950 PR 42
New-York Historical Society
- Series IV: Photographs, circa 1880s-1960s
  - Subseries IV.A: Small Photographs, 1885-1956 (bulk, undated)
    - United States (?), Cape Cod Canal Bridge, MA (Offsite-box 34)
      General and 3-dimensional model photos; Copies of renderings; Printed material
    - United States (?), Governor's Island, New York, NY (Offsite-box 34)
      General photos; Fort Jay Barracks: General and sculpture photos; Fort Jay Hospital; Copies of renderings; Newspaper clippings
    - United States Army War College, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 35)
    - United States Department of the Interior, National Park Service, White House Executive Offices, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 35)
      Photos; Correspondence; Copies of plans; Newspaper clippings; Printed material
    - United States Department of State, Building Competition, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 35)
      Copies of elevations, floor plans, and sections
    - United States Military Academy, Cullum Memorial Hall, West Point, N.Y. (Offsite-box 35)
    - United States Postal Service (Box 1 of 2), 1913, 1934-1935 (Offsite-box 35)
      New York Post Office, NY, NY: Exterior and Interior (1913) photos, Copies of renderings, Printed material, see also Large Photos, Box 1; New York Post Office Annex, Ninth Avenue and 33rd Street, NY, NY: Construction (1934-1935), Exterior and Interior photos, Substructure (photo album); see also Box 36: Newspaper clippings, Copies of renderings
    - United States Postal Service (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box 36)
      Schenectady Post Office, Schenectady, NY: Printed material
    - Universal Atlas Cement Company, Hudson, NY (Offsite-box 36)
    - University Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box 36)
      Photos; Department of Buildings documents; Printed material
    - University of Buffalo, Chemistry Building, Buffalo, NY (Offsite-box 36)
    - University of Connecticut, Storrs, CT, 1956 (Offsite-box 36)
    - University of Nevada, Mining Building, Reno, NV (Offsite-box 36)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, NC (Offsite-box 36)
      General photos; Dormitories; Library: Exterior and Interior photos; Manning Hall; Memorial Bell Tower; Copies of renderings; Printed material
    - University of Pennsylvania, Wharton School of Business, Philadelphia, PA, 1951-1952 (Offsite-box 37)
      Construction photos (1951-1952)
    - University of Rochester, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box 37)
      Eastman School of Music: Exterior, Interior and 3-dimensional model photos, Copies of floor plans and renderings, Printed material; Memorial Art Gallery: Exterior and Interior photos, Copies of renderings; Strong Memorial Hospital: Photos, Printed material; Copies of renderings; Printed material
    - University of Vermont, Burlington, VT (Box 1 of 2) (Offsite-box 38)
      General photos; Ira Allen Chapel; Men's and Women's Dormitories: Interior and Exterior photos, Copies of Renderings; Gymnasium and Field House; Library; Mary Fletcher Hospital: Aerieal, Exterior, Interior and Dormitory Room photos, Copies of plot plans and renderings, Newspaper clippings; Mabel Louise Southwick Memorial Building: Construction and Exterior photos; Waterman Memorial Student Union: General and 3-dimensional model photo
    - University of Vermont, Burlington, VT (Box 2 of 2) (Offsite-box 39)
      Waterman Memorial (cont'd): photos of a raised battleship, Notes, Blueprints and elevation drawings, Copies of plot plans, floor plans, renderings; Printer material
    - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA (Offsite-box 39)
    - Vanderbilt, Frederick W., Residence, Hyde Park, NY (Offsite-box 39)
      Exterior photos; Printed material
    - Vanderbilt, Mrs. William K. Jr., Townhouse, New York, NY (Offsite-box 39)
    - Vassar College, Poughkeepsie, NY (Offsite-box 39)
    - Vassar Hospital, Poughkeepsie, NY (Offsite-box 39)
    - Villard, Residence, 50th St. and Madison Ave., New York, NY (Offsite-box 39)
      Exterior and Interior photos
    - Wadsworth, James W., Residence, Geneseo, NY (Offsite-box 40)
    - Warren Building, 903-907 Broadway, New York, NY (Offsite-box 40)
    - Washington Memorial Arch, Washington Square, New York, NY (Offsite-box 40)
      General and sculpture photos; Printed material; see also Large Photos, Box 1
    - Wesleyan University, Middletown, CT, 1926-1938 (Offsite-box 40)
      General photos; Cemetery; Chemistry Building; Gymnasium; Olin Memorial Library: Construction (1926-1938), Exterior and Interior photos; Rich Hall: alteration photos; Photos of 3-dimensional models; Copies of renderings; Printed material
    - West Point Battle Monument, West Point, NY (Offsite-box 41)
      Photos; Copies of plot plans; Printed material
    - White, Bessie S., Residence, 110 Bleecker Street, New York, NY (Offsite-box 41)
    - White, Stanford (Offsite-box 41)
      Residences: New York, NY (Printed material) and St. James, NY
    - Whitney, Payne, Tombstone, Manhasset, NY (Offsite-box 41)
    - Whittemore, J.H., Naugatuck Fountain, Naugatuck, CT (Offsite-box 41)
    - Willard, Joseph E., Residence, 9 Sutton Place, New York, NY (Offsite-box 41)
    - Williams, Richard H. Jr., Residence Alterations, Mendham, NJ (Offsite-box 41)
    - Women's National Golf and Tennis Club, Glen Head, NY (Offsite-box 41)
      Exterior and Interior photos; Copies of renderings; Printed material
    - Woodlawn Trust Company, Woodlawn, PA, 1921 (Offsite-box 41)
      Exterior (1921) and Interior photos
    - World's Columbian Exposition, Agricultural Building, Chicago, IL (Offsite-box 41)
      Photos; Printed materials
    - World's Fair, Court of States, Flushing, NY (Offsite-box 41)
      General and 3-dimensional model photos
    - Wuhu Hospital, China (Offsite-box 41)
    - Yorktown Manor Hotel and Country Club, Yorktown, VA (Offsite-box 41)
    - Unidentified residences (Offsite-box 42)
      Miscellaneous photographs
    - National Commission of the Fine Arts publications, 1914-1934 (Offsite-box 42)
    - Miscellaneous printed material (Offsite-box 42)
  - Subseries IV.B: Medium Photographs, 1883-1941 (bulk, undated)
    This subseries includes 22 boxes of photographs approximately 11 x 14 in size.
    - Abbey, Francis Maria, Captain Thomas Abbey Memorial, Enfield, CT (Offsite-box 43)
    - Algonquin Club, Boston, MA (Offsite-box 43)
      Photos
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 629-635 W. 155th St., New York, NY (Offsite-box 43)
    - American Academy in Rome, Italy, 1920 (Offsite-box 43)
      Photos; Printed material (1920)
    - American Battle Monuments Commission (Offsite-box 43)
      American Military Cemetery, Florence, Italy
    - American University in Beirut, Lebanon (Offsite-box 43)
      Photo
    - Amherst College, Amherst, MA (Offsite-box 43)
      Aerial photos; Mead Art Museum; Various Buildings: Mounted and unmounted photos; Printed material
    - Andrews, John Forrest, Residence, Boston, MA (Offsite-box 44)
    - Appleton, Julia, Residence, Lenox, MA, 1884 (Offsite-box 44)
      Photo (1884)
    - Arlington Memorial Bridge Commission, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 44)
      Arlington Memorial Bridge: Photos, Printed material, Copies of renderings
    - Astor, John Jacob, Casino, Rhinebeck, NY (Offsite-box 44)
    - Athens Soldiers Monument, Athens, PA (Offsite-box 44)
    - Bank of Montreal, Montreal, Canada (Offsite-box 44)
    - Bank of Montreal, Winnipeg, Canada (Offsite-box 44)
    - Barber, Don, Hartford Times Building, Hartford, CT (Offsite-box 45)
    - Barnard College, New York, NY (Offsite-box 45)
    - Beard, Mrs. A. M. Residence, Tuxedo, NY (Offsite-box 45)
    - Bell, Isaac, Jr., Residence, Newport, RI, 1883 (Offsite-box 45)
    - Bellevue Hospital, New York, NY (Offsite-box 45)
      Photos; see also Large Photos, Box 1
    - Bennett, James Gordon Jr., New York Herald Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box 45)
    - Bethlehem Airport Terminal (Offsite-box 45)
    - Bethlehem Steel Company, 1941 (Offsite-box 45)
      Photos; Printed material (1941)
    - Blair, Edward Tyler, Residence, Chicago, IL (Offsite-box 45)
    - Bliss, Mrs. R.. W., Residence (Dumbarton Oakes), Washington, DC (Offsite-box 45)
    - Boston Public Library (Offsite-box 45)
    - Boston Symphony Hall (Offsite-box 45)
    - Bowdoin College, Brunswick, ME (Offsite-box 46)
      Walker Art Gallery: Photos
    - Bowery Savings Bank, New York, NY (Offsite-box 46)
    - Brearly School, New York, NY (Offsite-box 46)
    - Breese, James L., Residence, "The Orchard," Southampton, NY (Offsite-box 46)
    - Brooklyn Institute of Arts & Sciences (Offsite-box 46)
    - Burke, Winifred Masterson, Relief Foundation, Hospital, White Plains, NY (Offsite-box 46)
    - Burlington, City of, City Hall, Burlington, VT (Offsite-box 46)
    - Burney, Charles T., Residence, New York, NY (Offsite-box 46)
    - Butler, Joseph G., Jr., Butler Institute of American Art, Youngstown, OH (Offsite-box 46)
    - Century Association, Century Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box 46)
    - Century Holding Company, Apartment Building, 998 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box 46)
    - Cheney, Anne W., Residence, South Manchester, CT (Offsite-box 46)
    - Choate, Joseph Hodges P., Residence "Naumkeag," Stockbridge, MA (Offsite-box 46)
    - Church of Saint Paul the Apostle, Paulist Fathers Church, New York, NY (Offsite-box 47)
    - Cochran, Lucius, Memorial (Offsite-box 47)
    - Colony Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box 47)
    - Columbia Trust Company, 60 Broadway, New York, NY (Offsite-box 47)
    - Columbia University (Offsite-box 47)
      Avery Library; Casa Italiana; Earl Hall; Chemistry Building; Faculty House; Furnald Hall; John Jay Hall; Johnson Hall (Women's Dormitory); Kent Hall; Low Library (see also Large Photos, Box 1); Pan Statue; President's House; Pupin Hall; School of Journalism Building; Schemerhorn Hall; Miscellaneous
    - Commercial National Bank, Shreveport, LA (Offsite-box 48)
      Photostat of a photo; see also Large Photos, Box 2
    - Cook, Charles T., Residence, Elberon, NJ (Offsite-box 48)
    - Coolidge, T. J. Residence, Manchester, MA (Offsite-box 48)
    - Cuban American Sugar Company, Gramercy Refinery and Power House, Gramercy, LA (Offsite-box 48)
    - Dobbs Building, 618-20 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box 48)
    - Elks Club Lodge #22, 110 Livingston St., Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box 48)
    - Farragut Monument, New York, NY (Offsite-box 48)
    - Fayette National Bank, Lexington, KY (Offsite-box 48)
      Copy of floor plan
    - Federal Reserve Bank of New York (Offsite-box 48)
      Copies of competition drawings
    - First Methodist Episcopal Church, Baltimore, MD (Offsite-box 48)
    - Francklyn (Franklin), Charles G., Residence, Elberon, NJ (Long Branch, NJ) (Offsite-box 48)
    - Franklin National Bank, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box 48)
    - Frelinghuysen, Peter Hood, Residence and Garage, Morristown, NJ (Offsite-box 48)
    - French Consulate General Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box 48)
    - Gibson, Charles Dana, Residence, New York, NY (Offsite-box 48)
    - Girard Trust Company, Philadelphia, PA (Offsite-box 48)
    - Goelet, Robert, Mausoleum, Woodlawn Cemetery, Bronx, NY (Offsite-box 48)
    - Goelet, Robert, Residence, Newport, RI (Offsite-box 48)
    - Gorham Building, 386-390 Fifth Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box 48)
      Photos (see also Large Photos, Box 1 and Flat drawings); Printed material
    - Harlem Valley State Hospital, Wingdale, NY (Offsite-box 48)
      Copies of drawings and plans
    - Harvard Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box 48)
    - Harvard University (Offsite-box 49)
      Business School: Photos, Printed material, Newspaper clippings; Gates (various); Robinson Hall; Union
    - Home National Bank, Meriden, CT (Offsite-box 49)
    - Hooker, E. H., Residence, Greenwich, CT (Offsite-box 49)
    - Hooker Electrochemical Company, Niagara Falls, NY (Offsite-box 50)
    - Interborough Rapid Transit Power House, New York, NY (Offsite-box 50)
    - Johnson, Harold F., Residence, Louisville, KY (Offsite-box 50)
      Photos; Printed material; see also Large Photos, Box 2
    - Johnson, Harold F., Rule Memorial Chapel, Louisville, KY (Offsite-box 50)
    - Judson Memorial Church, New York, NY (Offsite-box 50)
    - Kane, John Innes (Offsite-box 50)
      Photos (detail of ceiling)
    - King's Mountain Battlefield Memorial, King's Mountain, SC (Offsite-box 50)
    - Knickerbocker Trust Company, New York, NY (Offsite-box 50)
    - Lawrence, William V., Hospital, Bronxville, NY (Offsite-box 50)
    - League for Political Education, Town Hall, New York, NY (123 West 43rd Street) (Offsite-box 50)
    - Lincoln Alliance Bank, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box 51)
    - Lincoln Monument, Chicago, IL (Offsite-box 51)
      Photo and copy of rendering of proposed position
    - Low, Carroll B. Residence, New Rochelle, NY (Offsite-box 51)
    - MacKay, Clarence Hungerford, Residence (Harbor Hill), Roslyn, NY (Offsite-box 51)
    - MacKay, Clarence Hungerford, Trinity Church, Roslyn, NY (Offsite-box 51)
    - MacKay, Clarence Hungerford, Trinity Church, Roslyn, NY (Offsite-box 51)
      Photos (Original Building and Second Building)
    - Madison Square Presbyterian Church, New York, NY (Offsite-box 51)
    - McKim, Charles F., Memorial Tablet in Harvard Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box 51)
    - McKinley Birthplace National Memorial Museum, Niles, OH (Offsite-box 51)
      Photos (see also Large Photos, Box 2); Printed material
    - Mechanics National Bank, Trenton, NJ (Offsite-box 51)
    - Metropolitan Club, 1 East 60th St., New York, NY (Offsite-box 51)
    - Metropolitan Museum or Art, New York, NY (Offsite-box 51)
    - Minneapolis Museum of Fine Arts, Minneapolis, MN (Offsite-box 52)
    - Morgan, Edwin Dennison, Residence, Beacon Hill, Beacon Rock, Newport, RI (Offsite-box 52)
      Photos; see also Large Photos, Box 2
    - Morgan, Edwin Dennison, Residence, Wheatley Hills, NY (Offsite-box 52)
    - Morgan, John Pierpont, Library, New York, NY (Offsite-box 52)
    - Munger, Robert Sylvester, Tombstone, Birmingham, AL (Offsite-box 52)
    - Munsey, Frank (Offsite-box 52)
      Photos: Various buildings
    - National Cash Register Company, Dayton, OH (Offsite-box 52)
      Auditorium: Photos
    - National City Bank, New York, NY (Offsite-box 52)
      Head Office at 55 Wall Street: Printed material; Branch at 15-17 42nd Street: Photos; Branch at 250 Fifth Avenue: Photos
    - National City Realty Company, 52 Wall Street, New York, NY (Offsite-box 52)
      Photo; Printed material
    - Naugatuck Church, Naugatuck, CT (Offsite-box 52)
    - Naugatuck Public High School, Naugatuck, CT (Offsite-box 52)
    - Nebraska, State of, State Capitol, Lincoln, NE (Offsite-box 52)
    - Newark Memorial Building, Newark, NJ (Offsite-box 53)
    - Newbold, Thomas, Residence, 15 East 79th Street, New York, NY (Offsite-box 53)
    - New England Trust Company, Boston, MA (Offsite-box 53)
    - New Haven Railroad, Waterbury Station, Waterbury, CT (Offsite-box 53)
    - Newport Casino, Newport, RI (Offsite-box 53)
    - New York, City of, Municipal Building, New York, NY (Offsite-box 53)
      Photos; Printed material; Statuary; see also Large Photos, Box 1
    - New York City Tunnel Authority, Brooklyn Battery Tunnel Ventilating Tower (Offsite-box 53)
      Photo; Copy of rendering
    - New York and Harlem RR Co., Apartment Building, 277 Park Ave., New York, NY (Offsite-box 53)
    - New York Institute for the Blind, Bronx, NY (Offsite-box 53)
    - New York Life Insurance Company (Offsite-box 54)
      Photos: Various Buildings
    - New York Post Graduate Medical School and Hospital, New York, NY (Offsite-box 54)
    - New York Public Library (Offsite-box 54)
    - New York University (Offsite-box 54)
      Cohen Memorial; Dental College; Hall of Fame; see also Large Photos, Box 1
    - Nickerson, George A., Residence, Commonwealth Ave., Boston, MA (Offsite-box 54)
    - Oakland, City of, City Hall, Oakland, CA (Offsite-box 54)
    - Oelrichs, Mrs. Hermann, "Rosecliff," Newport, RI (Offsite-box 54)
    - Olney, Richard, Residence, Boston, MA (Offsite-box 54)
    - Osborn, Charles T., Residence, Mamaroneck, NY (Offsite-box 54)
    - Osborn, Charles T., Mausoleum, Woodlawn Cemetery, Bronx, NY (Offsite-box 54)
    - Panama Pacific International Exposition, San Francisco, CA (Offsite-box 54)
    - Peabody, George, Peabody College for Teachers, Nashville, TN (Offsite-box 55)
    - Penn, William, Memorial Tablet, All Hallows Church, London, England (Offsite-box 55)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 1 of 3) (Offsite-box 55)
      Pennsylvania Station, New York, NY: Exterior Photos (Mounted and Unmounted)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 2 of 3) (Offsite-box 56)
      Pennsylvania Station, New York, NY, cont'd: Interior Photos (Mounted and Unmounted); Photos of sculptural models; Copies of renderings; see also Large Photos, Box 1
    - Pennsylvania Railroad (Box 3 of 3) (Offsite-box 57)
      Pennsylvania Station, Newark, NJ: Photo, see also Large Photos, Box 2; Pennsylvania Station, Pittsburgh, PA: Copies of rendering
    - Pennsylvania Terminal Real Estate Company, Hotel Pennsylvania, New York, NY (Offsite-box 57)
    - Pilgrim Society, Plymouth, MA (Offsite-box 57)
    - Pope, Alfred Artmore, "Hillstead," Farmington, CT (Offsite-box 57)
      Photos (Mounted and Unmounted)
    - Portchester, City of, Portchester (Offsite-box 57)
      Portchester Public Library: Copies of rendering; Portchester War Memorial: Photos
    - Princeton University, Princeton, NJ (Offsite-box 58)
      Athletic Field Gates: Photos; University Cottage Club: Photos
    - Prospect Park, Brooklyn, NY (Offsite-box 58)
    - Pulitzer, Joseph, Residence, New York, NY (Offsite-box 58)
    - Racquet and Tennis Club, 370 Park Avenue, New York, NY (Offsite-box 58)
    - Radcliffe College, Gymnasium, Cambridge, MA (Offsite-box 58)
    - Redmond, Geraldyn, Residence, New York, NY (Offsite-box 58)
    - Redmond, Johnston L, Residence, Tivoli, NY (Offsite-box 58)
    - Rhode Island, State of, State House, Providence, RI (Offsite-box 58)
      Interior and Exterior Photos; see also Large Photos, Box 2
    - Rochester Savings Bank, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box 59)
    - Royal Trust Company, Montreal, Canada (Offsite-box 59)
    - Russell, Mrs. Henry E., Mausoleum, Woodlawn Cemetery, Bronx, NY (Offsite-box 59)
    - Russell, H. E. and C. B. Erwin, Russwin Hotel, New Britain, CT (Offsite-box 59)
    - Saint Bartholomew's Church, New York, NY (Offsite-box 59)
    - Saint Luke's Hospital, Duluth, MN (Offsite-box 59)
    - Saint Peter's Church, Morristown, NJ (Offsite-box 59)
    - Saulte Sainte Marie Monument, Falls Canal, MI (Offsite-box 59)
    - Savoy Plaza Hotel (Offsite-box 59)
    - Schenectady, City of, City Hall, Schenectady, NY (Offsite-box 60)
    - Scholz, Mrs. Belle Kinney, Statue, Boiceville, NY (Offsite-box 60)
    - Schuyler, Philip, Tombstone (Offsite-box 60)
    - Seventh Regiment Armory, Tiffany Room, New York, NY (Offsite-box 60)
    - Shaw, Colonel Robert Gould Memorial, Shaw Memorial, Boston, MA (Offsite-box 60)
    - Shepard, Elliott Fitch, Residence, "Woodlea," Scarborough, NY (now Sleepy Hollow Country Club) (Offsite-box 60)
    - Sherman, William T. Monument platform, Grand Army Plaza, New York, NY (Offsite-box 60)
    - Sherry, Louis (Offsite-box 60)
      Hotel, Fifth Avenue, New York, NY; Restaurant and Shop, 25 East 62nd Street, New York, NY; see also Large Photos, Box 1
    - State Savings Bank, Detroit, MI (Offsite-box 60)
    - Taylor, Henry A. C. (Offsite-box 60)
      Townhouse at 3 East 71st Street, New York, NY; Mausoleum, Woodlawn Cemetery, Bronx, NY; see also Large Photos, Box 1
    - Tennessee, State of, Tennessee War Memorial, Nashville, TN (Offsite-box 60)
    - Tiffany & Company, Tiffany Building, 397-409 Fifth Ave., New York, NY (Offsite-box 60)
    - Tomb of Unknown Soldier (Offsite-box 60)
    - Trinity College, Hartford, CT (Offsite-box 60)
    - Union & Planters Bank, Memphis, TN (Offsite-box 61)
    - Union Savings Bank, Fall River, MA (Offsite-box 61)
    - United Nations, United Nations Headquarters, New York, NY (Offsite-box 61)
      Copies of renderings by Webb and Knapp
    - United States Army War College, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 61)
    - United States Department of the Interior, National Park Service, White House Executive Offices, Washington, DC (Offsite-box 61)
      Printed material; Album; see also Box 62: Exterior and Interior photos
    - United States, Governor's Island, New York, NY (Offsite-box 62)
    - United States Military Academy, West Point, NY (Offsite-box 62)
      Cullum Memorial Hall; Battle Memorial
    - United States Postal Service (Offsite-box 62)
      New York Postal Office, New York, NY: Exterior and Interior photos; Printed material
    - University Club, New York, NY (Offsite-box 62)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill, NC (Offsite-box 62)
      Exterior and Interior Photos; Printed material
    - University of Rochester, Rochester, NY (Offsite-box 63)
      Album; Photos; Printed material
    - University of Vermont (Offsite-box 63)
      General photos; Mary Fletcher Hospital; Printed material
    - University of Virginia, Charlottesville, VA (Offsite-box 64)
    - Vanderbilt, Frederick W., Residence, Hyde Park, NY (Offsite-box 64)
    - Vanderbilt, Mrs. William K., Jr., Townhouse, New York, NY (Offsite-box 64)
    - Villard, Henry, Residence, New York, NY (Offsite-box 64)
    - Ward, James, Memorial (Offsite-box 64)
    - Washington Memorial Arch, Washington Square, New York, NY (Offsite-box 64)
    - White, Stanford, Monument (Offsite-box 64)
    - World's Columbian Exposition, New York State Building, Chicago, IL (Offsite-box 64)
    - Yorktown Manor Hotel and Country Club, Yorktown, VA (Offsite-box 64)
    - Miscellaneous buildings by Lawrence White (Offsite-box 65)
      Album; see also Large Photos, Box 1
    - Miscellaneous buildings by J. K. Smith (Offsite-box 65)
      Album
    - Miscellaneous printed material (Offsite-box 65)
      2 folders
    - Unidentified buildings (Offsite-box 65)
      Photos and copies of renderings
    - Non-McKim, Mead and White buildings (Offsite-box 65)
      Thomas G. Appleton House by Richard M. Hunt; Trinity Church, Boston – design by Stratton; Casino by Stratton
  - Subseries IV.C: Large Photographs, undated
    This subseries includes 3 flat boxes of oversize photographs.
    - Unidentified interior (Box 66)
    - Harvard Club, exterior (Box 66)
    - Pennsylvania Station, photograph of a drawing (Box 66)
    - Pennsylvania Station, photograph of a plan (Box 66)
    - Pennsylvania Station, interior, photograph of a drawing (Box 66)
    - Louis Sherry, 2 exteriors (Box 66)
    - Lawrence Grant White House, 277 Park Avenue, 3 exteriors (Box 66)
    - Hall of Languages, NYU, exterior (Box 66)
    - Columbia University, aerial view (Box 66)
    - Goelet Office Building, 2 exteriors (Box 66)
    - Colony Club, exterior (Box 66)
    - Brooklyn Elks Lodge, exterior? (Box 66)
    - Tiffany Building, exterior (Box 66)
    - University Club, exterior (Box 66)
    - Group Portrait of Office (Box 66)
    - Low Library, Alma Mater (Box 66)
    - Interborough Power House (Box 66)
    - Franklin National Bank (Box 66)
    - New York Athletic Club, exterior (Box 66)
    - New York Life Building, exterior (Box 66)
    - Sherry Building, exterior (Box 66)
    - Goelet Building, exterior (Box 66)
    - Russel Erwin Building, exterior (Box 66)
    - Joseph Pulitzer House, exterior (Box 66)
    - Gibson House, exterior (Box 66)
    - Freundschaft Society, exterior (Box 66)
    - Municipal Building, 5 views of the exterior (Box 66)
    - King Apartment House, 139th St., 2 views of the exterior (Box 66)
    - H.A.C. Taylor House, exterior (Box 66)